智媛
JI-WON
杀了我
Kill me.
我的命运终究是要死在朴敏焕手上吗？
Was I destined to die in Park Min-hwan's hands?
智媛
Ji-won.
智媛！
Ji-won!
等等，等一下
Wait. Hold on...
你说一次看看
Tell me again.
我以后不接李在元的电话
I won't answer Lee Jae-won's calls.
就算他到家里来，也不要开门
If he comes to the house, I won't open the door,
然后马上打电话给你
and call you right away.
李室长
Mr. Lee.
感谢你每次都载我到医院来
Thank you for driving me to the hospital every time like this
也感谢你和我洽谈离婚事宜…
and giving me divorce advice, but--
你不必感谢我
You don't have to thank me for that.
这是我的业务
It's work for me.
U&K付我很多钱
I get paid a lot of money from U&K.
我只是照着雇主的要求去做
I do what my employer wants.
好
Okay.
不过你说过你关心我
But you said you cared about me.
你还是把想说的话都说出来了
You just have to say your piece.
请等一下
Just a moment.
刘志赫部长
GENERAL MANAGER YU JI-HYUK
喂？怎么会这个时间打给我？
Hey, what is it at this hour?
我现在在警察局
I'm at the police station.
警察局？
The police station?
我现在马上过去
I'll be right there.
不用到这里来，请你到医院去
No, go to the hospital instead.
唯一医院
YUIL MEDICAL CENTER
第15集
EPISODE 15
区域紧急医疗中心
不好意思
Excuse me.
姜智媛，32岁，从江南的U&K总公司送过来的这位患者在哪里？
Kang Ji-won, 32, transferred from U&K in Gangnam. Where is she?
亲爱的
Ji-won.
她的呼吸和脉搏都恢复正常了
Her breathing and pulse are stable now.
稍微有点发烧，等她恢复意识，我们会再过来看看
But she has a fever, so we'll check her once she wakes up.
由于是暴力事件，她跟警察一起过来，我开诊断书给你们
It was an assault, so she came with the police. I'll get you her record.
喂
Hey.
我会终结你的人生
I'm going to ruin your life,
做好心理准备
so brace yourself.
我会向媒体爆料富三代施暴又仗势欺人
I'll tell the media a third-generation tycoon assaulted me.
现在这个时代，你隐瞒不了的
You can't cover things up these days.
我已经惨到不能再惨了
I have nothing to lose now.
都是因为你
Thanks to you.
为了姜智媛而毁了你的人生会不会太逊了？
But isn't Ji-won too inferior to ruin your life over?
她瘦巴巴的，有什么看头？
She's nothing but skin and bones.
刘部长
Mr. Yu.
要我给你一个忠告吗？
Do you want some advice?
不要太相信她
Don't trust her.
你知道我为何会疯掉吗？
Do you know why I went mad?
姜智媛会让人发疯
Ji-won makes people lose their minds.
毁掉你的不是我和姜智媛
Ji-won and I aren't the ones that ruined you.
是你的垃圾品行
It's your trashy personality.
把人打成这样，你的品行就很高尚吗？
Look how you beat me. Is your personality any better?
你不能因为比我会打架就这样
You can't do this because you fight better.
你才是不该那样对待体重只有你一半的女人吧？
That's a bit rich, considering what you did to a woman half your size.
什么？
What?
对你不利的时候，你就寻求平等
You seek equality when at a disadvantage,
对你有利的时候，你就爱展现力量
and strength when at an advantage.
其实我不喜欢运用我的力量
I hate using my strength.
可是对你，我不得不用
But not to you.
刘志赫先生，请出来
Mr. Yu, you can come out.
走吧
Let's go.
那我呢？
What about me?
为什么不把我弄出去？
Why can't I come out?
我呢？
What about me?
你以为你的人生不能再惨了吗？
Do you really think you can't go any lower?
大错特错
You're wrong.
不，为什么只有有钱人可以出去？
No, wait. Is it because he's rich?
我也是U&K的人
I work at U&K too!
那我呢？
What about me?
有钱没罪，没钱有罪！
One law for the rich and another for the poor!
朴敏焕从今天起被解雇
Min-hwan is fired as of today
事由是对同事施暴，违反公司规定
for assaulting a colleague and violating the rules.
也再找找其他事由
Find anything else.
上次出轨事件时，我有查过了
I checked during his affair incident.
他还有擅离职守、使用公司信用卡明细不清
AWOL and unclear corporate card statements.
不当招待厂商的情况
And he illegally treated clients.
很好，他是不是有公司贷款？
Good. Doesn't he have a company loan?
我会要银行向他提出还款要求
I'll ask the bank for a repayment request.
我会把暴力、伤害等可以加的罪名都加上去
I'll add assault, injury, and anything else.
还有姜智媛…
And Ms. Kang is...
她现在在家里
She's at home.
这是她的意愿
It's what she wanted.
我刚好和杨珠兰科长在一起
I happened to be with Ms. Yang.
所以我让杨科长去陪她，不过她看起来不太好
So I left Ms. Kang with her, but she didn't look good.
朴敏焕是不是也有欠高利贷没还？
You said there was a debt that Min-hwan hadn't paid off, right?
施压要他还钱
Put some pressure on that.
我们买下债权也可以
Or buy the bonds.
我马上去查
I'll look into it.
刘部长
Mr. Yu.
智媛怎么样了？
How's Ji-won?
她不太好
She's not good.
我想她睡一觉会比较好，所以想让她喝点牛奶
I think she'll be better if she sleeps, so I'll get her some milk.
可是家里什么都没有
There's nothing in her house.
部长，你还好吗？
Are you okay?
嗯，还好
Well, yes.
谢谢你，现在由我来接手，你回去休息吧
Thank you. I'll take it from here. You should go home and rest.
志赫
Ji-hyuk.
对不起
I'm sorry.
全都是我不好
I'm sorry for everything.
你有没有受伤？
Were you hurt?
这边怎么了？
What's this?
你好
Hello.
问候就只有这样？
Is that all?
也太少了吧
It can't be.
你打来是因为你先生受我照顾
Considering you called because your husband's in my care,
只说这样也太少了吧
there should be more.
你们要不要到中国去一阵子？
How about going to China for a while?
唉唷，那我们当然感激不尽
Oh, my. We would be so thankful if you could do that for us.
不过你们搭船的时候，会有些辛苦
It'll be a rough ride on the ship though.
唉唷，那怎么会辛苦呢？我们都没把您吩咐的事给办好
That's nothing at all. We couldn't even get the job done.
如果您再给我一次机会
If you give us another chance,
我会用力踩油门，把她辗过去
I'll hit the accelerator and crush her.
请一定要联络我
So just let me know.
好，谢谢
Yeah, thank you.
没钱的人总会试图留下些东西
Poor people always try to keep a record.
手上必须要握有保险
As insurance.
你想要的是什么？
What do you want?
你不喜欢我好好照顾你爸吗？
Do you hate that I'm taking care of your father?
只要把姜智媛辗过去的简单事情变得不再简单了
Now that crushing Kang Ji-won isn't so simple anymore,
你就突然要我们什么都别做
you suddenly say, "Don't do anything."
之后朴敏换还突然说要离婚
Then Park Min-hwan suddenly asks me for a divorce,
而我爸又不接电话，我就明白了
and my dad won't pick up, so I realize,
这样下去，只有我会完蛋
"I'll get screwed over."
从你的表情看来
Judging by the look on your face,
有钱人也没多厉害
you're nothing special.
可恶，我不该窝在房间里的
Darn it. Why have I been cooped up at home like that?
换我问问题了
I ask the questions now.
你能为我做什么？
What can you do for me?
韩国的小虾米是有毒吗？怎么会这么没有分寸？
Are the shrimps in Korea poisonous? Why don't they know their place?
郑万植和裴熙淑的尸体被发现了吗？
Have the bodies of Jeong Man-sik and Bae Hui-suk been found?
我会去查警方的报告
I'll check the police report.
暂时不要让新闻报出来
Make sure there's no news about it.
让郑秀敏感到有危机变得没好处了
Jeong Su-min shouldn't feel threatened now.
朴敏焕和郑秀敏
Park Min-hwan and Jeong Su-min.
可以一次解决掉吗？
Can we take care of them both at once?
朴敏焕
PARK MIN-HWAN
喂？
Hello?
我现在在警察局
I'm at the police station right now.
不好意思，可以请你帮个忙吗？
I'm sorry, but can I ask for a favor?
什么？警察局？
What? The police station?
首尔城三警察局
SUNGSAM POLICE STATION
虽然把你弄出来了，但是这个案子有些严重
We got you out, but it's pretty serious.
我们可能罩不了你
We may not be able to cover it.
什么？那是什么意思？
What? What are you saying?
你没有事先跟我们商量过，就做出这种行为
It wasn't what we agreed on.
若我们与U&K正面对决，副社长的负担会很大
If we have to fight U&K head-on, the burden on Ms. Oh will be big.
喂！
Hey!
你那是什么讲话态度？你以为你是谁啊？
What's with the attitude? Who do you think you are?
你是云彩航空的副社长吗？
You're not the VP of Cloud Air!
喂
Hey.
你也不是
You're not either.
所以不要这么没礼貌
So don't be rude.
可恶
Damn it.
只在擂台上打架的家伙，就只会耍嘴皮子
You only know how to fight in the ring. Watch your mouth.
你不过就是吴宥拉的小喽罗
You're just Yu-ra's henchman.
还敢对我颐指气使
Don't act like you're my boss.
混账
Bastard.
先生，等一下
Mister, wait!
你为什么要把他打到流鼻血？
Why would you give him a nosebleed?
我有什么理由不能那么做吗？
Is there a reason I can't?
那家伙的态度很糟糕啊！
He gave me attitude!
可恶
Damn it...
他只是太过担心我了
He's just worried about me.
今天你老婆来威胁我
Since your wife came and threatened me today.
很可怕
It was scary.
什么？威胁什呢？
What? About what?
她说你要离婚，她不愿意自己一个人死
She said you asked for a divorce. She won't go down alone.
她说不会让你独自脱身
She won't let you get away alone.
她疯啦？真是的
Is she out of her mind? Damn it.
等等
Hold on.
U&K人事总管
U&K HR DEPARTMENT
我公司打电话来了，先挂电话吧，我等一下再打给你
Work's calling me. Hang up. I'll call you back later.
喂？
Hello?
朴敏焕先生，我要通知你，你从今天起被解雇了
Mr. Park, I called to say you're fired as of today.
由于你目前没有来上班
You didn't come to work today,
因此法务组已经派人递交书面解雇通知书到你府上
so the legal team has sent someone to deliver your written dismissal.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
你公司有人过来，你怎么会被解雇？
Someone from your workplace is here. You're fired?
你到底在做什么啊？
What on earth have you been doing?
在此通知您
I am calling to inform
您以U&K在职作为担保的最低利贷款偿还义务即日起生效
your obligation to repay the U&K guaranteed loan is effective as of today.
该死
Damn it!
这个混蛋干嘛一直打来？
Why does he keep calling?
毒蛇金融
SNAKE LOANS
- 先生 - 嗯？
- Sir. - What?
你为什么不接电话？
Why won't you pick up?
一旦信任消失
When the trust is gone,
我们就会开始写抛弃身体切结书
we get a physical rights waiver signed, you see.
对于借钱不还的家伙
For those who don't pay back money,
要戳哪个洞，钱才会出来？
which hole should we poke to get it back?
洞？什么洞？
Hole? What hole?
那些黑道混蛋
Those damn thugs.
拜托
Please.
秀敏
Su-min.
可恶
Crap.
该死
Damn it...
我有买股票
I did stocks.
我赚了不少
I earned quite a lot.
拜托，秀敏
Please, Su-min!
拜托你有钱，拜托…
Have some money. Please!
好，电子凭证…
I need her certificate...
拜托要有
Please, be there.
有有有！
It's there!
她有电子凭证
Her certificate's here!
接着是密码，密码是多少？
What's her password?
秀敏，拜托你有钱
Su-min, please have some money.
拜托
Please!
80,230,537韩元
（人民币43万2553元）
八千万韩元？
She has 80 million won?
80,230,537韩元
（人民币43万2553元）
她怎么会有这么多钱？
Why does she have so much?
她拿走了要给她爸的钱？
She stole the money for her dad?
她真的不是一般厉害
She's really something.
刘志赫部长
GENERAL MANAGER YU JI-HYUK
刘志赫部长？
Mr. Yu?
唯一医院
YUIL MEDICAL CENTER
你要告我通奸？
Sue me for adultery?
你要告我？
You?
哇哦
Damn...
天啊
I mean...
- 请叫保全过来 - 你真的是…
- Call security. - How could you?
这位家属，不可以在医院吵闹
Sir, you can't do this here.
医师
Doctor.
- 医师 - 你喝醉了吗？
- Doctor. - Are you drunk?
医师，我是她的丈夫
I'm her husband.
可是她躲在这里，也不接电话
But she was hiding here and ignoring my calls.
还告我通奸
And she sued me for adultery.
又没有证据
Without evidence.
有证据
I have it.
你真的想这样？
Do you really want to do this here?
在医院里？
At the hospital?
怎样？
What do you have?
行车纪录器？
The dashcam recording?
没有影像的那个？
There's no video.
珠兰
Ju-ran.
大姐！
Ju-ran!
你没办法用那个跟我离婚
You can't divorce me with that!
要看得到画面，让人无法抵赖
You must have the video. Hard evidence.
- 请你出去 - 不要拦我
- Let's get you outside. - Come on.
你要让妍芝没有爸爸吗？
Yeon-ji will be fatherless because of you.
你是谁？搞什么？放开我！
Who are you? What's going on? Let go!
你没有认真看离婚诉状
Did you even read the divorce papers?
李锡俊
Lee Seok-jun.
我是杨珠兰的律师
I'm Ms. Yang Ju-ran's lawyer.
律师？
Lawyer?
我会声请保护令
I'll apply for a restraining order.
不要再来了
Never come back.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
嗯
Yes.
负责手术的医师很有实力，又有自信
The doctor is good and confident about the surgery,
- 你不用太担心 - 对了
- so don't worry. - Right.
智媛还好吗？
Is Ji-won okay?
据我所知，她没事
As far as I know, yes.
不过请你也担心一下自己
But you should worry about yourself.
好久不见了
It's been a while.
我很惊讶你会突然联络我
I was so surprised to get your call.
许久不见，见到你真高兴
It's nice to see you after so long.
要点餐吗？
Can I take your order?
你过得好吗？
Have you been well?
嗯，过得很好
Yes, I have.
其实我过得不好
To be honest, I'm not doing that well.
朴敏换和我决定要离婚了
Min-hwan and I are getting a divorce.
昨天我离开家里，现在住在楼上
I left the house yesterday. I'm staying upstairs.
想休息一阵子
I'm going to rest for now.
这是因果报应
It must be karma.
我被爱情蒙蔽了双眼
Blinded by love, I betrayed
背叛了我唯一的闺蜜，我的另一半
my only best friend.
结果…
In the end...
总之我现在是一个人了
Anyway, I'm all alone now.
你说你要离婚，那事情变得容易许多
The divorce makes this easier to say.
你打算要杀了姜智媛吧？
Did you try to kill Ji-won?
换作是我也会这么做
I would've done the same.
我的意思是说 我知道姜智媛和朴敏焕
I'm saying I know Ji-won and Min-hwan are
又重新在一起了
seeing each other again.
他们两个…
Are they really...
真的重新在一起了？
seeing each other again?
告他们通奸罪吧
Let's charge them with adultery.
我会告诉你何时跟如何进去
I'll let you know when and where to go.
如果你有需要的话 我也会帮你找最好的律师
If you want, I'll get you the best lawyer too.
你就只需履行身为法定配偶的权利
You just fulfill your role as his legal spouse.
为什么要帮我？
Why?
我不服气
Because it's not fair.
你的人生不是由于朴敏焕而毁了吗？
Isn't your life ruined because of Min-hwan?
要是你离婚 你就拿不到之前在公司工作的补偿
If you divorce, you won't be rewarded for your work at the company.
你什么都不剩
You'll be left with nothing.
我…
That's true...
的确是如此
for me.
那你能得到什么？
But what do you gain?
我希望姜智媛回到我身边
I want to get Kang Ji-won back.
我喜欢姜智媛
I like Ji-won.
所以我讨厌她跟朴敏焕纠缠
So I hate that she's with him.
我会想办法让她回到我身边
I'm going to make her come back to me.
所以帮帮我
So help me.
我可以问你一件事吗？
Can I ask you something?
你为什么讨厌我？
Why do you hate me?
因为你只知道自己
Because you're selfish.
有的人会啃食身边的人
There are those who gnaw at people around them.
而你正是这种人，所以我很讨厌
You are that type, so I hate you.
你又不了解我
You don't know me that well.
你不相信任何人吧？
You don't trust anyone, do you?
那是因为你是不值得信任的人
That's because you're not trustworthy.
你认为别人也跟你一样 所以你无法相信人
You think everyone's like you, so you can't trust anyone.
你这么想，我们怎么合作？
How can you work with me thinking like that?
你不是问我为什么讨厌你吗？
Didn't you ask me why I hated you?
我没说我无法与你合作
I never said I couldn't work with you.
你决定好就告诉我
Let me know when you decide.
谈得很顺利
It went well.
如你所说，她问我为何要帮她
As you said, she asked me why I was helping her.
如果我全都说谎，她应该不会相信 所以我适当地掺入一些真话
I didn't think she'd believe me if I lied, so I mixed in some truth.
除了她会发现出轨的一对 是吴宥拉和朴敏焕之外
Except that it'll be Oh Yu-ra and Park Min-hwan instead,
我说的全都是事实
everything I said was true.
还有…
Also...
我们公司有提供给员工一项保险
There's an insurance policy provided to company employees.
家人保险
A family insurance.
理赔对象包括本人、配偶与直系血亲
It compensates yourself, spouse, and immediate family.
离职时，本人可以决定是否继续加保
You can decide to keep it when you quit.
二手市场
SECOND HAND MARKET
过不久应该就会通知朴敏焕
A notice will go to Park Min-hwan soon.
把这个卖了，就可以救急
I can take care of the more urgent debt if this gets sold.
他本来不晓得有这种保险
He doesn't know such insurance existed,
不过很快就会知道了
but he will soon.
舞台正在搭建中
The stage is being set.
糖果
我要不要干脆去死？
Shall I just die?
虽然如果朴敏换没有起歹念 那项保险就没有用
Though it's useless if Min-hwan doesn't decide to die.
要是我死了
If I die...
我爸妈就能领到我的身故保险金
my mom and dad can get my life insurance benefit.
在朴敏焕走到现在这步之前 有好几次机会可以停止
Min-hwan could've stopped several times on his way here,
但是他都没有
but he didn't.
他应该会一路走到底
He'll go all the way.
那就没有问题了
Then there's no problem.
郑秀敏应该也会一路走到底
Jeong Su-min will go all the way too.
为什么大家
Why is everyone
都只在找姜智媛？
looking for Kang Ji-won?
因为现在的郑秀敏 应该会对你更加执着
I think Jeong Su-min is more obsessed with you right now.
现在就剩那一刻了
It's that moment now.
剩下的就是让郑秀敏经历那一刻
All that's left is for her to experience it.
要不要回日本呢？
How about returning to Japan?
比起以前，刘志赫行动积极许多
Yu Ji-hyuk is moving more actively than before.
他把朴敏焕个人的债务和高利贷
He's pressuring Park Min-hwan
全都买下来，向他施压 他应该撑不久
with his debt and private loans. He won't last long.
他似乎也不放弃寻找郑万植和裴熙淑
And he hasn't given up on Man-sik and Hui-suk.
他搜遍了 仁川所有废弃工厂附近的监视器画面
He got all the CCTV footage from the abandoned factory.
虽然他不会找到什么
He won't find anything,
但是与U&K正面迎战，没有任何好处
but nothing good can come from fighting U&K head-on.
看来你没信心
You must not be confident.
你已经先害怕，要我逃跑了
Seeing how you're telling me to run away.
没关系
It's okay.
他爷爷不一样
His grandfather is different.
他与温室花朵刘志赫不一样
Unlike Ji-hyuk, who's like a flower in a green house,
他是很现实的人
he's realistic.
他知道灰姑娘会多么令人头疼
He knows how much of a nuisance Cinderella can be.
将军
Checkmate.
我都赢不过爷爷
I can never beat you.
因为你全都想要，就被我看穿步数了
You want everything, so I can read your hand.
懂得放弃不属于自己的东西 是作为领导者的条件
A good leader should know how to give up something that's not theirs.
好
Okay.
你来啦？
Hey!
嗯
Hi.
我和爷爷在下象棋
We were just playing janggi.
今天我又输了
And I lost again.
不过我觉得我应该能赢过你 要一起下吗？
But I think I can beat you. Do you want to play?
爷爷
Grandfather.
您不是要我带喜欢的女生回来吗？
You asked me to bring the woman I like.
我会正式带她过来
I will introduce her to you.
所以请不要再让宥拉到家里来了
So don't let Yu-ra into the house anymore.
你之前说你是单恋，没打算跟她交往
You said it was one-sided and weren't going to make it work.
你改变心意了吗？
Did you change your mind?
对，我打算跟她在一起
Yes, I'm going to pursue it.
可是家里不能有前未婚妻进出
So I can't have my ex-fiancée frequenting my house.
我在订婚期间太不用心了
I was so indifferent during our engagement.
我都不晓得他这么急性子
I didn't know he was so impatient.
像我们这样的人
People like us
结婚不是我们说好就可以
can't marry for love, can we?
别做鲁莽的举动 先获得爷爷的同意…
Get permission from your grandfather before you--
我会的
I will.
我现在就把她介绍给您
I'll introduce her now.
您好，我是姜智媛
Hello, I'm Kang Ji-won.
我们来把姜智媛处理掉
Let's get rid of Kang Ji-won.
你不要回日本吗？
You're not going back to Japan?
我输了会活不下去
I can't live with myself if I lose.
我为何要被微不足道的小虫 害得我有这种感觉？
Why do I have to feel this way over those cockroaches?
对，当初我就应该亲自出手
Yeah, I should've done it myself.
借他人之手只是让自己头痛
It's a headache having others do it.
我告诉自己 必然会发生的事，就算困难也要面对
I've decided to face the obstacles that are bound to happen.
上次我跟你见面的时候
When I met you last time,
有些话没有告诉你
there's something I didn't tell you.
并不是面对就能解决所有事情
Powering through isn't a solution to everything.
我知道我孙子给了你 许多作为短暂交往的回报
I'm aware he gave you a lot for seeing him briefly.
所以你以后打算怎么做？
So what are you going to do from now on?
我会回过头去看和反省我有没有做错
I'll look back and reflect on my faults.
能够改正的就改正
I'll correct what I can.
剩下的…
And the rest...
我想我也无可奈何
I guess it is what it is.
现在差不多是你想你也无可奈何 然后退出的时候了
It's time for you to step back and say, "It is what it is."
您果然知道这件事
So you knew.
我为了这件事狠狠骂了刘志赫
I gave him hell for that.
不会再有这种事了
That won't ever happen again.
他真的有很多不足
He lacks so much.
您对他娇生惯养
You spoiled him.
他只知道工作，对钱完全没有概念
He only knows how to work. He has no concept of money.
其实他太过富家少爷的态度 令我不知所措
Honestly, I was flustered because he was like a rich boy.
你是想要说什么？
What are you trying to say?
可是我喜欢他这一点
But I liked that about him.
其实我也是有很多不足的人
To tell you the truth, I lack a lot too.
当我以为他是完美的富三代的时候
When I thought he was a perfect third-generation chaebol,
感觉他遥不可及
he seemed unreachable.
可是当我看到他傻气、生气、散漫
But he can be foolish, get angry, and messy.
不知所措，以及有时…
He gets embarrassed, and sometimes...
耍孩子气的样子
he acts like a baby. Seeing those sides of him,
我想我们可以好好在一起
I thought we could do well together.
我想要跟他一起过得幸福
I want to be happy with him.
爷爷
Sir.
请把刘志赫交给我
Please, give Yu Ji-hyuk to me.
所有关于朴敏焕解雇的事宜 明天就会处理完毕
Park Min-hwan's termination will be finalized by tomorrow.
不过你为什么要问 公司帮忙加保的员工保险呢？
By the way, why did you ask about the insurance for employees?
通常他们都不会继续加保
They don't usually keep it.
这只是一项公司福利 大部分的人根本不知道有这个东西
It's just a company perk. Most don't know about it.
朴敏焕必定会继续加保
Park Min-hwan will do it.
看起来好好吃
That looks good.
三个
Three.
味道和口感如何？
How's the taste and texture?
确实如你所说 菠菜海螺意大利面最受欢迎
As you predicted, the spinach pasta with sea snails was most popular.
这应该会成为主打商品
It'll be the main product.
太好了
That's good.
在韩国的意大利面里 不常使用海螺与波菜…
Sea snails and spinach aren't common ingredients for pasta in Korea...
哦，对了
Oh, right.
请看镜头
Look at the camera.
好
Okay.
很好
Yes, that's good.
放轻松就好
Just be comfortable.
他会拍下自然的模样
He's going to get a natural look.
刘熙妍
YU HUI-YEON
今天真是辛苦你了
Great job today.
不会啦，你解救了差点失业的我 我才要感谢你
It was nothing. You saved me from being unemployed. I appreciate it.
我会尽快把修改好的食谱传给你
I'll send you the recipe revisions soon.
- 有点难呢 - 好
- It's hard. - Yeah.
我也会把草案和工厂时程 整理好传给你
I'll send you the draft and factory schedule too.
好
Okay.
对了
By the way,
今天没有看到刘熙妍和刘志赫
I didn't see Yu Hui-yeon and Yu Ji-hyuk today.
刚才部长一直都在啊
Mr. Yu was there all day.
这么说来，今天没看到熙妍耶
I haven't seen Hui-yeon either.
她去哪了？
Where did she go?
那我先走了
I should get going.
- 路上小心 - 好
- Goodbye! - Bye!
郑秀敏
JEONG SU-MIN
拒绝接听
CALL DECLINED
郑秀敏
JEONG SU-MIN
拒绝接听
CALL DECLINED
为什么不接我电话？
Why not pick up my calls?
我问你为何不接我电话
Why won't you pick up?
我为什么要接你电话？
Why do I have to pick up your calls?
好吧，我可以理解
Yeah, I get it.
你跟我老公交往了七年 结果他却选择了我，而不是你
You were with him for seven years, but he chose me over you.
你肯定一时很难接受
I'm sure it was hard to accept.
就算是这样
But still,
你怎么可以勾引已婚男子？你害得我要离婚了
how could you seduce a married man? I'm about to get divorced because of you.
请问是警卫室吗？
Is this security?
这里是16楼
This is the 16th floor.
有外部人士进来
An outsider is here.
请你们尽快处理
Take care of her.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
你以为我会坐视不管吗？
Do you think I'd let it slide?
喂
Hey.
我为何要跟别人的男人搞在一起？我又不是你
Why would I sleep with someone else's man? I'm not you.
哦，你是用这种方式勾引了朴敏焕 所以你应该很清楚
Right, you seduced Min-hwan this way, so I'm sure you know best.
可是如果他是会背叛 交往七年女友的人
But if he betrayed his girlfriend of seven years,
你怎么会不知道 他也可以对你这么做呢？
why didn't you know he could do the same to you?
我会在公司贴大字报 让你们俩在公司里都抬不起头来
I'll put posters up here to make you two too ashamed to work here.
我不会放过你
I won't stand for it.
这可怎么办才好？
That's too bad.
你老公已经被这个公司开除了
Your husband was fired.
所以别在这里无谓地怀疑我 回去当个贤内助，对哦
So stop suspecting me, and go be a good wife. Oh, wait.
你们要离婚了吧？
You two are divorcing.
真糟糕
That's too bad.
不过…
But...
我越想越觉得不高兴
thinking about it is pissing me off.
只有你才会贪图朴敏焕这种垃圾
Only you would covet trash like Min-hwan.
我怎么会呢？
Why would I?
除非我是个傻子才会吧
Unless I was a fool.
放手，我自己走，放开我！
Let go. I'm going. Let me go!
敏焕，刚才郑秀敏来公司大闹 吓到我了
Min-hwan, Jeong Su-min just came and caused a fuss. It scared me.
不过公司不会谣传什么八卦 因为大家都只在说郑秀敏是不是疯了
But rumors won't spread here since everyone thinks Su-min's crazy.
唉呀，不小心传错了，抱歉
Oh, no. I sent it to the wrong person. Sorry.
她真的是疯了！
Is she out of her mind?
我不会放过她
I won't stand for this.
郑秀敏很快就会打给我了
Jeong Su-min will call me soon.
郑秀敏
JEONG SU-MIN
我要毁了姜智媛
I'm going to ruin Kang Ji-won.
你大可拥有她
Have her.
但是在那之前 我一定要让她跌到谷底
In return, she has to hit rock bottom first.
我要让她向我求饶
I'll make her beg.
在那之前，我不会合作
I won't cooperate before that.
郑秀敏上钩了
We have Su-min in our hands.
我来让朴敏焕行动
I'll try to move Min-hwan.
他现在差不多应该收到了
I think he's gotten it by now.
海英别墅
HAEYEONG VILLA
U&K寄了什么给我？
What would U&K send me?
U&K人寿，保险单
U&K LIFE INSURANCE POLICY
开什么玩笑？
What the heck?
我都被公司开除了 哪有钱可以缴保险费？
I was fired. I have no money to pay for this.
保障事项：配偶伤害死亡，五亿韩元（人民币269万6420元）
SPOUSE'S DEATH AFTER INJURY 500 MILLION WON
你可能没有理由要罩我
You may not have a reason to cover for me,
可是我们可以交易
but we can make a deal.
我来解决郑秀敏，让她不会再来烦你
I'll take care of Su-min so she won't bother you.
再准备一份餐点
Tell them to bring one more meal.
我们先吃再来谈
Let's eat first.
所以你要怎么处理你老婆？
So how will you take care of your wife?
我现在是穷光蛋，正打算要去死
I'm broke, so I was going to kill myself.
可是出现生路了
But there's a way to live.
而那条生路也可能对你有帮助
And I think that might help you too.
保障事项：配偶伤害死亡，五亿韩元（人民币269万6420元）
SPOUSE'S DEATH AFTER INJURY 500 MILLION WON
这要配偶死亡才能领到
You can only get this after death.
只要郑秀敏消失在这个世界上
If Su-min disappears,
就不会有人威胁你了
there won't be anyone to threaten you.
当然这不容易，我们也得套好说法
It won't be easy. We have to get our story straight.
不过你是不是能帮我呢？
But can't you help me?
又要我帮你收拾善后？
You want me to clean up your mess? Again?
不只是收拾善后
Not just that.
你还得帮我布局
Set it up for me too.
这个世界上金钱和人脉就是一切 而我一个都没有
Money and connections are everything, but I don't have any of them.
你有胆量
You've got guts.
很多东西都没有的话，至少要有胆量
If you don't have anything, you should at least have guts.
可是你是不是只有胆量？
But isn't that all you have?
你以为做这种决定很容易吗？
You think it was easy to decide?
这是我的最后防线
This is my last resort.
我得赌上性命
I'll risk my life.
这是你最后一次机会
This is your last chance.
现在朴敏焕在吴宥拉的套房里
Park Min-hwan is at Oh Yu-ra's suite right now.
所以就是今天了
So it's today.
郑秀敏
JEONG SU-MIN
朴敏焕和姜智媛 温顿饭店，1355号房
Park Min-hwan and Kang Ji-won are in room 1355 at Winton Hotel.
1355号
Room 1355.
让开
Move.
话说亲爱的，你真的好聪明哦
But I think you're really smart, babe.
话说这还真天才
But that is pretty genius.
你怎么会想到 要以老婆的身故保险金东山再起？
Going after your wife's life insurance benefit?
你怎么会想到要投保癌症保险啊？
How did you think of cancer insurance?
等到我领到保险金，我请你大吃一顿
Once I get paid, I'll treat you to something nice.
不用担心
Don't worry.
我这个人可是非常会报恩
I know how to return the favor properly.
吓我一跳
Oh, my God!
可恶
Damn...
不管是谁，都有够无言
Whoever it is, this is ridiculous.
喂，朴敏焕
Hey, Min-hwan.
你真的是个无法处理的垃圾
You're a piece of trash that can't be handled.
不然你是要怎样？
What are you going to do about it?
对哦
Right?
我要把那段录音交给警方
I'm going to send the voice recording to the police.
我爸在哪里？你杀了他吗？
Where's my dad? Did you kill him?
杀了他？
Kill him?
我以为你要和姜智媛复合
I thought you were trying to get Ji-won back.
你和这女的在这里做什么？
What are you doing here with her?
听说你也被公司开除了
I heard you were fired.
既然你时间这么多 你们俩就去吃牢饭吧
Since you have a lot of free time, spend it in jail.
那个疯女人
Are you insane?
滚开，滚！
Get lost!
放开我，我叫你放开我！
Let go of me!
放手！
Let go!
该死
Damn it...
现在该怎么办？
What do I do now?
还能怎么办？
What do you mean?
就照你的计划去做
We'll go forward with your plan.
但是不能在这里
But not here.
我会帮你布局
I'll set it up for you.
副社长
Ms. Oh.
假如朴敏焕杀了郑秀敏
If Park Min-hwan kills Jeong Su-min,
就定调为谋杀妻子以诈领保险金
set it up as murder for the insurance claim
编好故事之后，发给媒体
and distribute it to the media.
我会去准备，可是…
I'll get it ready, but...
要让朴敏焕说的关于我的事 都变成是在胡扯
Make sure whatever he says about me is nonsense.
证据当然也要消灭
Get rid of all the evidence, got it?
你这是在做什么？
What do you think you're doing?
所以说你为何要做那种无谓的事？
So why did you do something like that?
你什么都好，就是没有自知之明
You're great, but you don't know your place.
我有钱，我全都给你
I have money. I'll give it all to you.
要是你杀了我
If you kill me,
你想那女的会放过你吗？
do you think she'll leave you alone?
郑秀敏
Su-min.
我承认你很厉害
I'll give it to you.
你真的有让吴宥拉抵赖不掉的证据
You really have hard evidence on Oh Yu-ra.
可是怎么办才好？
But too bad for you.
你昏倒的时候，吴宥拉把它全删了
She erased it when you passed out.
什么？
What?
你这个傻瓜
You dummy.
像我们这种人
People like us shouldn't
不能跟有权有势的人作对
go against people with power.
我们能做什么？
What can we do?
还有…
And...
你没有钱
you have no money.
零韩元
0 WON
什么？为什么？
What's that?
反正那本来就不是你的钱
It wasn't your money anyway!
你是趁机占为己有
You stole it when you had the chance.
对了
Oh, right.
我买给姜智媛的包包在你那里
You had the bag I bought for Ji-won.
我卖掉了
I sold that.
你得先帮你老公救急啊
To take care of urgent matters for me.
不要觉得太委屈
Don't be too upset.
你不是说不愿意自己一个人死吗？
You said you wouldn't go down alone.
不是你死，就是我死
One of us has to die.
站在我的立场来看
So...
我得先解决掉你才能重新开始
I have to take care of you to start over.
你等着
Just wait.
喂！放开我！
Hey! Let me go!
放开我！
Let me go!
放开我！把我放开！
放开我！
Let me go!
把我…
Let me...
把我放开
Let me go!
喂！
Hey!
瓦斯…
The gas...
她去哪了？
Where did she go?
喂！
Hey!
你疯啦？
Are you crazy?
交出车钥匙，滚到一边去
Leave the car key and move aside.
好，我知道了，你先冷静
Okay. Just calm down.
把刀放下，拜托你冷静！
Put the knife down! Calm down!
我不会死
I won't die.
我绝不会死！
I'll never die!
来
Here.
车钥匙给你
Here's the key.
车钥匙在这里，你把刀放下
Here it is. Put the knife down.
快点过来拿
Just take it!
拿走，来
Take it. Here.
去死
You little...
过来
Come here.
给我过来！
Come here!
可恶
Damn it...
我可爱的妻子来旅行
My lovely wife's going to
大概是在我去买东西的时候
die from carbon monoxide poisoning
由于锅炉故障，一氧化碳中毒而死
from a boiler malfunction while I'm away to get groceries.
所以别再毁了我的人生
So stop ruining my life.
该死的时候就乖乖去死
Just die already.
喂，要死你自己乖乖去死
Hey! If you're going to die, just die already.
原来保险金是在说这个啊
This is what the insurance was about?
你以为会如你所愿吗？
You think it'll go your way?
我想是会
I think it will.
可恶！
Damn it!
我老公可不能当不了男人啊
My husband shouldn't lose his manhood.
可恶
Damn it...
真是的
You little...
不对
No.
喂，姜智媛跟我说
Kang Ji-won told me
你是太监
that you were sterile.
你在胡说什么？
What are you talking about?
你当不了男人！
You're shooting blanks!
要我讲简单一点吗？
Want me to spell it out?
我不是流产
I didn't miscarry.
我不曾怀孕过
I was never pregnant.
你听懂了吗？
Do you get it now?
你别想
I don't think so.
- 竟敢… - 放开我，你这个混蛋！
- You little... - Let go, you bastard!
- 给我过来！- 放手！
- Come here! - Let go!
我叫你放手！
Let go of me!
- 滚开！- 滚开！
- Get lost! - Get lost!
杨珠兰科长的离婚诉讼 似乎会变得容易许多
I think Ms. Yang's divorce suit will get easier.
作为成立通奸罪证据的存储卡影像 不知道为什么复原了
The evidence of the affair on the SD card, I don't know why, but it's been restored.
- 突然间吗？- 对
- Suddenly? - Yes.
本来就是无缘无故没有影像
The video didn't work for no reason.
突然之间又无缘无故好了
It suddenly worked for no reason too.
会成的事就是会成 看来他们是注定要离婚
I guess they're just meant to get a divorce.
朴敏焕先生离世，仅此转达讣闻 地点：唯一医院殡仪馆
THE LATE PARK MIN-HWAN'S FUNERAL YUIL MEDICAL CENTER FUNERAL HALL
我查看了警方的报告
I checked the police report.
他的死因是摔倒在玻璃桌上 头部撞到桌脚
He fell over a glass table and died after hitting his head.
由于现场留有证据，警方认定 郑秀敏是头号嫌犯，正在寻找中
With the evidence, the police are looking for Jeong Su-min as the prime suspect.
可是监视器没有运作
But the security cameras didn't work,
还需要再查明确切情形
so they must find out what happened.
你要去…
Are you going...
参加丧礼吗？
to the funeral?
我曾经想过要是你死了就好了
I thought about how nice it would be if you died.
在我气到快死
I thought I'd burst of anger then.
当失望变成绝望
Back when those disappointing times
并且确定是背叛的时候
were confirmed with despair and betrayal.
你今天好美
You look so beautiful today.
可恶
This little...
滚开！
Get lost!
去死
Just die.
我想了一整夜，怎么想也想不通 你为何要对我那样
I spent all night wondering why you were like that to me.
没想到却这样结束了
But it ended like this.
你怎么敢来这里？
How dare you come here?
要不是你背叛我们家敏焕
If you didn't betray Min-hwan,
他就不会跟秀敏那女人结婚了
he never would've married Su-min.
她杀了我儿子
She killed my son.
坏女人
That wench.
怎么会…
How could this...
她毁了我宝贝儿子的人生
She ruined my precious son's life!
我可怜的孩子
My poor boy!
24日在京畿道加丰面的一家民宿中
At a pension in Gyeonggi Province on the 24th,
发现30多岁朴姓男子的尸体
Park, a man in his thirties, was found dead.
警方认定其妻子郑姓女子是头号嫌犯
The police confirmed his wife, Jeong, is the prime suspect.
这是行销一组的郑秀敏吧？
Isn't this Jeong Su-min from marketing?
之前那个
Don't you remember?
不是吧，只是长得像吧
No, they just look alike.
那你是说死掉的丈夫是朴敏焕吗？
Are you saying Min-hwan's dead?
你在说什么？嘘
What? Keep it down.
我听说是耶
I hear it's him.
喂
Hey...
怎么回事？
What's this?
朴敏焕的父母报案遭窃 小偷趁他们不在时进来
Park Min-hwan's parents reported a theft. A thief came in while they were away.
看来是郑秀敏
It was Jeong Su-min.
那表示她在首尔
That means she's in Seoul.
警方通缉 加丰面民宿杀人案的嫌犯郑秀敏
It's been a day since the police put out an APB
已经过了一天
on Jeong Su-min, the prime suspect,
依旧没能掌握到她的行踪
but her exact whereabouts are still unknown.
- 警方认为… - 没关系
- The police - It's fine.
目前她关掉手机，躲避搜查，逃亡中
assume she's off the grid and on the run
并且表示需要国民积极关注本案
and ask for the citizens' active cooperation for the case.
嫌犯身高160公分，身材瘦弱
The suspect is 160 cm tall with a lean physique
涉嫌在加丰面的一家民宿 杀害丈夫朴姓男子
and under suspicion of killing her husband at a pension.
可是我有点不安
But I feel uneasy.
你太善良了，所以你也许不知道
You're too nice, so you wouldn't know.
但就是有些人不懂得适可而止
Some people don't know when to stop.
如果不把他们彻底狠狠踩在脚底下
Unless you stomp on them completely,
他们不会停止
they don't stop.
你不能丢下我，独自幸福，智媛
You can't be the only one who's happy, Ji-won.
绝对不行
Never.
我做了什么？
What did I do?
- 你有证据吗？- 接受惩罚吧
- Do you have proof? - Pay for what you did.
我不会软弱
I will stay strong.
我也会再加把劲
I'll try a little harder too.
她买稀释液，表示她要纵火
She bought thinner. That means she'll set a fire.
不让她来有什么用？
What's the use of stopping her from coming?
我们已经照你想做的去做了 这次让我照我想做的去做吧
We did what you wanted. Let me do what I want this time.
事到如今，还能怎么样？
We can't do anything about it now.
你为何都只想着自己？
You always think only about yourself.
我真的是为了你，学了各种东西
I learned so many things because of you.
姜智媛，我要杀了你！
I'm going to kill you!
这是你造孽的代价 也是我打造的地狱
This is the price for your sins and hell I made for you.
接受吧
Take it.
翻译：彭向棻
Translated by Suyun Mounce